# CAMILA BERTOLANI

Full Stack Developer

### **About me**

I am an IT professional with experience in Frontend and Backend development, knowledge in Information Security, teamwork and effective communication skills. I consider myself responsible, creative, with initiative, focused on innovation and development of new technologies. I am interested in continuing to learn and expand my skills in the IT area.

### **Contact**







## **Education**

2019

Computer Technician

• 200 hours of internships and programming internships

Instituto técnico industrial San judas Tadeo

Advanced Web Development UTN (E-Learning UTN)

2020

Lic. en informática (in progress)

Universidad nacional de

Hurlingham

Flutter: Desarrollo para IOS y

Andrioid

Framework JS: Angular, Vue y

React Udemy

2022

Fundamentals of Hacking and Defense

Ekoparty Hackademy



## **Personal Data**

- Date of Birth: 25/09/2000
- Marital Status: Single
- Ituzaingó, Buenos Aires, Argentina

## Professional Experience

Codes S.A 2020-2020

Software Engineer

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- C# NFT
- SQL Server Management

Southern Horizon 2021-2022

Full Stack Developer

- React, Angula
- C#..NET
- SQL Server Management, GIT

Santander Tecnología

Software Engineer

- Deact
- C#..NET. Prisma. Node JS. Next J
- PostgreSQL, GIT

IT Patagonia

Full Stack Developer

React, Angular

2022-Present

2022-2023

### Skills

- C#/.NET Core
- Node JS
- SQL Server
  Management
- MySQL
- MariaDB
- Typescript

- Angular
- React
- Dart
- Flutter
- Burp Suite
- Nmap
- Nessus

# Languages

- Español
- Inglés
- Japonés



## **Hobbies**

- Judo
- Swimming